A Guide to the William Garber Photograph Collection, 1930-1960
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- View of six of the trucks belonging to Triplett and Vehrencamp. Mount Jackson, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0022; 8x10
- Six Triplett and Vehrencamp trucks, with seven men posing next to them. Mount Jackson, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0023; 8x10
- Duplicate of P0002.05.0023.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0023a; 8x10
- Duplicate of P0002.05.0023.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0023b; 8x10
- Duplicate of P0002.05.0023.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0023c; 8x10
- Portrait of police officer Charley Grabill.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0024; 5x7
  Series 13f, “Photograph Prints: Police Officers and Fire Stations, Box 5, Folder 8,” begins.
- Portrait of police officer Charley Grabill.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0025; 5x7
- Front view of the Broadway Volunteer Fire Department, with three different types of fire trucks sitting in front of it.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0026; 8x10
- Broadway Volunteer Fire Department, possibly an open house. A man standing behind a podium, with three other men sitting behind him.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0027; 8x10
- Broadway Volunteer Fire Department, possibly an open house. Five men and one woman posing behind a podium.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0028; 8x10
- Duplicate of P0002.05.0028.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0028a; 8x10
- Duplicate of P0002.05.0028.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0028b; 8x10
- Broadway Volunteer Fire Department, possibly an open house. Three men posing behind a podium.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0029; 8x10
- Nine women posing in a kitchen at the Broadway Volunteer Fire Department, pouring and holding beverages. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0030; 8x10
- The Edinburg baseball team, posing on the front steps of a large building.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0031; 8x10
  Series 13g, “Photograph Prints: Baseball, Box 5, Folder 9,” begins.
- The Edinburg baseball team posing in a grassy area, surrounded by trees and bushes.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0032; 8x10
- The Edinburg baseball team posing in a grassy area, surrounded by trees and bushes.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0033; 8x10
- Baseball team with the letter “E” printed on their uniforms posing with a young child and a dog in a grassy area surrounded by trees.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0034; 8x10
- Baseball team with the letter “E” printed on their uniforms posing with a young child and a dog in a grassy area surrounded by trees.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0035; 8x10
- Duplicate of P0002.05.0035.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0035a; 8x10
- Baseball team with the letter “E” printed on their uniforms posing with a young child and a dog in a grassy area surrounded by trees.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0036; 8x10
- African-American baseball team from Elkton, posing on a baseball field with other players in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0037; 8x10
- New Market baseball team, probably the New Market Rebels, posing in front of the fan stands.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0038; 8x10
- Quicksburg baseball team (probably of the Valley Twin County or Rockingham County Leagues), posing in front of a fence that is advertising Shenandoah Sports and Appliances in Woodstock, Va. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0039; 8x10
- Quicksburg baseball team (probably of the Valley Twin County or Rockingham County Leagues), posing on a baseball field with fans in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0040; 8x10
- A baseball team with the letter “S” on their uniform, posing in front of a fence advertising for businesses in Woodstock, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0041; 8x10
- The Timberville Hatchery baseball team posing inside of a home or other building.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0042; 8x10
- The Woodstock baseball team posing in front of a fence advertising for businesses in Woodstock, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0043; 8x10
- Broadway Horse Show, a man posing on a horse with a trophy in his hand.1949, Image: P0002.05.0044; 8x10
  Series 13h, “Photograph Prints: Broadway Horse Show, Box 5, Folder 10,” begins.
- Broadway Horse Show, a man posing on a horse with a ribbon in his hand, and woman standing next to him.1949, Image: P0002.05.0045; 8x10
- John Deere Day, five men and two women posing behind a counter that is advertising John Deere repair parts.1947, Image: P0002.05.0046; 8x10
  Series 13i, “Photograph Prints: John Deere Day, Box 5, Folder 11,” begins.
- John Deere Day, two men standing next to a long table where seven women and one small girl are serving doughnuts and other refreshments. John Deere decorations and large crowds can be seen through the window behind them.1947, Image: P0002.05.0047; 8x10
- John Deere Day, view of a large crowd gathered around the tractor displays outside of a John Deere store.1947, Image: P0002.05.0048; 8x10
- Employees of the Shenandoah Valley Electric Cooperative posing next to a truck and a few pieces of equipment.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0049; 5x7
  Series 13j, “Photograph Prints: Miscellaneous, Box 5, Folder 12,” begins.
- Two African-American men sitting inside of a small wooden home; the one man is posing at a table while writing, while the other poses from the bed, where she is reading.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0050; 8x10
- A man posing next to a small airplane that has “(Tyler) Flight Service, Massapequa Park, N.Y., Insect Control” painted on the side of it.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0051; 8x10
- Four men working on the construction site of a large building.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0052; 8x10
- A fairly large gathering of people, mostly men, that are well dressed and standing on the side of a road, possibly for church.c. 1930-1940, Image: P0002.05.0053; 8x10
- A jazz band called “The Music Mac’s”performing on a small wooden stage that is lined with automobile tires.c. 1930-1940, Image: P0002.05.0054; 8x10
- A display of Hotpoint kitchen appliances.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0055; 8x10
- Close up view of a large farm.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0056; 8x10
  Series 13k, “Photograph Prints: Aerial Photographs, Box 5, Folder 13,” begins.
- View of a small airport, possibly owned by Owen Showalter.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0057; 8x10
  “Airport—Owen Showalter” handwritten in pencil on the back.
- Close up view of a large poultry farm, probably Hill Top Hatchery, that is surrounded by trees.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0058; 8x10
  “Hill Top Hatchery” handwritten in pencil on the back.
- Close up view of a fairly large industrial site.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0059; 8x10
- Close up view of Highway Motors, an automotive shop and service station.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0060; 8x10
  “HiWay Mot.” handwritten in pencil on the back.
- A close up view of Harrisonburg High School, which is now Memorial Hall of James Madison University.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0061; 8x10
  “HHS #1” handwritten in pen on the back.
- Houses, fields, and farmland in Luray, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0062; 11x14
  “Luray” handwritten in pencil on the back. See “Oversize Negatives” folder in Box 5, Folder 14.
- An expansive view of the urbanized area of Luray, Va., with fields and farmland in the distance.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0063; 11x14
  “Luray” handwritten in pencil on the back. See “Oversize Prints” folder in Box 5, Folder 14. Photograph is torn.